The Dr. Octopus to my Spider-Man.
- The Dr. Sivana to my Captain Marvel...
- Okay, I get it, I get it, I get it.
It's amazing how many super villains
have advanced degrees.
Graduate schools should do a better job
of screening those people out.
(Penny:)Sheldon, come back. You're losing me.
It's Leslie Winkle, Penny.
She belittles my research.
(Penny:)Oh, sweetie, I'm sorry.
She called me "dumb-ass."
(Penny:)I know, I heard.
Given the situation...
(Sheldon:)...I have no choice
but to withdraw my previous objections...
...to your ill-considered relationship
with Leonard.
Oh, gee, well, thank you for that.
(Penny:)But, um, I think for now
Leonard and I are just gonna stay friends.
(Sheldon:)No. That response is unacceptable to me.
(Penny:)- You are a smart guy. You must know...
- I'm smart?
(Sheldon:)I'd have to lose 60 IQ points
to be classified as "smart."
- Are you gonna let me talk?
- I'm sorry.
(Penny:)You must know that if Leonard and Leslie
wanna be together...
...nothing you can do is gonna stop it.